<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enterprise on Community Pulse</title>
    <link>http://communitypulse.io/tags/enterprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enterprise on Community Pulse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://communitypulse.io/tags/enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>After Pulse: Big Company, Little Company</title>
      <link>http://communitypulse.io/32ap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://communitypulse.io/32ap/</guid>
      <description>Sponsored by: IBM Developer Are you building cloud applications with Java, AI, Machine Learning, Serverless and Containers? IBM Developer provides a large number of Code Patterns, sample applications, articles, tutorials and videos to help you build faster. All code is available on GitHub. You can incorporate any code into existing applications or use it to start a new application. Simply go to developer.ibm.com to access IBM Developer resources and start building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Company, Little Company - The Differences in DevRel at Large and Small Companies</title>
      <link>http://communitypulse.io/32-bigco-littleco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://communitypulse.io/32-bigco-littleco/</guid>
      <description>Check Outs  Jason  Tribes: We Need You to Lead Us by Seth Godin The Art of Gathering: How We Meet and Why It Matters by Priya Parker  Matt  DevRel is company-specific. Every company has different needs and different expecations. Discover what your company needs and then find others who are in similar places so that you have people to watch and learn from.  Nathen  Trapeze School New York Be in awe of the work others do, regardless of what that work is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>